# VINITA WADHWA

# UI/UX DEVELOPER

#### PERSONAL SUMMARY

I am a **UI/UX developer** who is proficient in **back-end**, **front-end** and **design** frameworks. My passion lies in not just learning but also applying latest technologies. A self motivated developer with significant experience having worked on a **number of projects**. A passionate and hardworking individual with a penchant for meeting deadlines and **handling pressure**.

#### KEY COMPETENCIES

HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, React JS, MongoDB, NodeJS, ExpressJS, C, C++, C#, Java, MySQL, Photoshop, Adobe XD Lean Application Development End-to-End Testing Project Management Process Optimization

#### CONTACT DETAILS

Mumbai, India

Email: wadhwavinita8@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://bit.ly/linkedin-vinita

#### WORK REFERENCES

Shailesh Dugar Leader Engineering Team - Ulysses Systems LinkedIn: https://bit.ly/linkedin-shailesh

#### **INTERESTS**

Food Blogging - Instagram: non\_stop\_cravings

#### WORK HISTORY

### **Software Developer**

ULYSSES SYSTEMS | SEP 2017 - MAR 2019

- Developed a Project (Overlay) which is an ambitious upcoming project of Ulysses. It can be seen as a knowledge management application for any domain that is armed with path breaking AI facilities that aim to revolutionize how knowledge management used to be.
- Two domains that I participated in are:
  - Emergency Response System for Schools
  - Excursion Assistant
- Collaborated with designers, business analysts and other developers to develop and deploy applications.
- Wrote **efficient**, **well-designed code** and maintained software documentation.

## **Professional Level Instructor**

WHITEHAT JR. | JAN 2020 - PRESENT

 Instructing students in programming principles, concepts, and in-depth subject matter for trending web and mobile based technologies.

# ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

#### **University of Mumbai**

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING, COMPUTER ENGG. 2014-2017

- Graphics Editor Indian Society for Technical Education.
- Event Head Utsav, University of Mumbai
- Event Coordinator Tiecon, Mumbai Chapter

#### **Udemy**

The Complete Web Developer Bootcamp